praguepost.com 2019-11-08

# Privacy Policy | Prague Post

Privacy Policy applies to all of the services provided at the [Praguepost.com](https://www.praguepost.com/) web sites. This Privacy Policy is subject to change.

## 1\. Collected information

Praguepost.com does not utilize any third party advertising networks. Therefore, we do not store any behavior data, nor we track any user’s activities when they leave Praguepost.com website.

Praguepost.com is hosted on WordPress CMS ( Content Management System ) free to use software. WordPress is a non-profit organization, offering free to use open source software for web developers. It means that Prague Post has no control over what user or visitor data WordPress gathers. To read further information about what data WordPress gathers, please refer to the below page:  
<https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/>

**Affiliated sites:** Praguepost.com has an affiliation with Amazon.com and Booking.com for some products or services. We insert some affiliate links to some of our pages to earn commissions from products or services that Amazon.com and Booking.com offers. The affiliate links do not store or track any user data. These links provide traffic data for Amazon.com and Booking.com to know where the traffic is coming from to reserve the commission. The use and privacy at those sites are subject to their terms of use and privacy policies when you click and visit their websites. For further information, please visit the below websites:  
<https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.html>  
<https://services.amazon.com/content/Privacy_Policy.html>

Prague Post only uses Clicky traffic monitoring software to see where and how the users arrive at the landing pages. Information we collect is used only to enhance our services, to perform research and to develop further. The only information Prague Post gathers are; the IP address of the visitor, where they landed from, which pages the visitor visits. We do not track, trace, monitor any other information when the visitor leaves Praguepost.com website. To read about the Clicky privacy policy, please visit the below page:  
<https://clicky.com/help/faq/privacy>

## 2\. Personal information and sharing

We only see user email addresses or names when they directly contact Prague Post via email or using the contact form. Personal information you provide is used only according to this Privacy Policy. You can decide not to provide the information, but we may not be able to reply to your queries. We do not disclose user information to any third party unless it is required or enforced by law.

 **Updated on 25 May 2018, to comply with the GDPR ( The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union. )**
